A Guide to the Thomas H. Arthur Papers, 1953-2018: SC 0088
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Series 2: Scholarship and Teaching, 1970-2014
  - Subseries 2.1: Melvyn Douglas Research, 1970-1982
    - Programs from Early Performances (Folder 5 of 6), 1979 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Programs from Early Performances (Folder 6 of 6), 1979 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Arthur's manuscripts, Part 1, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Arthur's manuscripts, Part 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Copy of Douglas' outline on acting, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Douglas' handwritten notes for biography, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Photographs (Folder 1 of 3), undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Photographs (Folder 2 of 3), undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Photographs (Folder 3 of 3), undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 2.2: Study Abroad Semester Materials, 1979-2014
    - London and Italy Ephemera, 1979-2014 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Teaching Materials and Itineraries, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Photographs and Postcards, 1984, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)